whymilk.com 2001-06-02

# Milk - Cruise for Calcium

**MILK'S WEB SITE AND PRIVACY POLICY**

**PRIVACY POLICY**  
This site ("Milk") has a policy to respect and protect the privacy of its users. This privacy policy statement tells you how we collect information from you and how we use it. Using the Internet should be a fun experience and we want to help you make it so. 

The information you provide to Milk will not be disclosed to third parties without your consent. Milk may share aggregate information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties (for example, what percentage of our visitors are male and what percentage are female). This data is used to customize the content and advertising on our site and to deliver a better experience for our users. 

There are cases where Milk may request personal information such as your name, e-mail address and birth date. For example, we request personal information when you request information, brochures or information on diet and exercise, or for services that require registration (for example, entrance in a sweepstakes or joining Club Milk).

Milk needs to collect this information for complying with your requests, fulfilling prizes, tracking/verifying compliance with Milk policies as well as federal, state, and local laws, and/or for editorial and feedback solicitation purposes. We will not use any personal information for any purpose except for its intended use, which shall be disclosed at the time such information is requested. 

We provide a link to www.gotmilk.com web site to make it convenient for you to purchase "Milk" merchandise. The www.gotmilk.com web site is owned and controlled by the California Fluid Milk Processor Advisory Board. We do not have control over this web site, the information collected on this web site or the manner in which such information is used. Please refer to the www.gotmilk.com privacy policy to learn how your personal information will be collected and used by the California Fluid Milk Processor Advisory Board.

In case you change your mind or some personal information changes (such as your ZIP code), we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update, or remove the personal data you give us. You can do this at the member information page or by contacting our Customer Support organization at milk@bsmg.com.   
Milk may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Milk's rights or property, other Milk users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Milk may also disclose user information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

**OPTING OUT**  
Information provided at the time of registration or submission from a guest who is 13 years of age or over may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by Milk. To keep you in control of your personal information and the communications directed to you, you may opt out of receiving communications from Milk about new features or services. If you object to such use for any reason, you may stop that use by e-mail request to milk@bsmg.com. To opt out of receiving information from www.gotmilk.com, please refer to the California Fluid Milk Processor Advisory Board's privacy policy.

**POLICY FOR KIDS (INDIVIDUALS UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE)**  
Milk encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the activities offered on the sites. No information should be submitted to or posted at Milk by guests under 13 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian. Unless otherwise disclosed during collection and parental/guardian consent is obtained, Milk does not provide any personally identifying information, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever from our guests under 13 years of age.

When a guest under 13 registers for a sweepstakes, contest or Club Milk, he/she will be required either to: (a) provide the e-mail address of his/her parent or guardian and that parent or guardian will receive an e-mail alerting them to that registration, or (b) print the registration/entry form and mail it in with a parent/guardian signature. 

Unsolicited requests for information on a one-time basis will be honored without parental consent, and any personal information used for purposes of responding will not be retained or used for any other purpose. Registered guests under 13 years of age may participate in activities on our site upon registration (such as participation in Club Milk or entry into a sweepstakes), unless their parent or guardian asks that their registration be invalidated.

In order for the potential member to use the Milk interactive services, the parent or guardian must validate the account, as described in the e-mail. No information collected from guests under 13 years of age is used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside Milk, except as explicitly stated during registration for contests or promotions (and in that case, the information collected is used only for the specific contest or promotion). 

Although guests under 13 years of age may be allowed to participate in some contests and promotions, if such a guest wins, notification and prizes are sent to the parent or guardian identified in the initial registration process. Publication of names, ages, or images for promotion winners under 13 require parental or guardian consent.

**POLICY FOR TEENS (INDIVIDUALS 13 TO 17 YEARS OF AGE)**  
Guests who are 13 to 17 years of age should seek parental consent before providing any personal identifying information on our site.

**USE OF IP ADDRESSES**   
An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers -- the big computers that "serve up" Web pages -- automatically identify your computer by its IP address. Milk collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to our promotional partners, and to audit the use of our site. 

When guests request pages from Milk sites, our servers log the guests' IP addresses. We do not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a user's session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our house rules or terms of service or to protect our service, site, customers, or others. 

**USE OF COOKIES**   
What are cookies? Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at our site. We never save passwords or credit card information in cookies. 

The use of cookies is an industry standard -- you'll find them at most major Web sites. By showing how and when guests use a site, cookies may help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. We may use the information from cookies to provide services better tailored to our users needs. Milk has two primary uses for their cookies. 

First, we may use them to specify unique preferences. This way you don't have to tell us over and over again about the kinds of information you want to see. Secondly, we use cookies to track user trends and patterns. This helps us better understand and improve areas of the Milk service that our users find valuable.   
While both of these activities depend on the use of a cookie, visitors to Milk always have the option of disabling cookies via their browser preferences.

Information from cookies is sometimes attached to messages sent to our Customer Service department. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of the Milk service will not function properly or may be considerably slower if you refuse cookies. For example, without cookies, you will not be able to set personalized news preferences or you may have difficulty completing shopping transactions, entering contests, or playing games. 

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES**  
Users should be aware that when they are on Milk, they could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from Milk pages that take you outside our service. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement or wish to purchase milk gear or gifts on www.gotmilk.com, the "click" takes you off the Milk site. This includes links from advertisers and partners that may use Milk or the Milk's logo as part of a co-branding agreement.

These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online that information can be collected and used by people you don't know. While Milk strives to protect their users' personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk. 

Milk's policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond Milk's control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation.

**SECURITY**  
The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our Guests is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Milk can't ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk.

Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. When credit card information is transmitted we use industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. Your Milk Account is password-protected so that only you can access it and view the member information relevant to the account. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Milk will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or e-mail.

ltimately, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. Remember to sign out of your Milk or Milk Account and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if your computer is accessible to others or if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet café. 

**UNSOLICITED MATERIALS**  
Please note that it is our policy not to accept or consider unsolicited creative, production-related or other materials of any kind. We appreciate your cooperation in adhering to this policy. 

**DISCLAIMERS AND LIMITATION OF LIABILITY**   
We make no representations or warranties of any kind as to: (a) the accuracy or completeness of the information or materials on the site and assume no responsibility for any errors or omissions in its content; (b) the availability for use of any copyrighted, trademarked or proprietary materials of third parties that may appear in this site; (c) computer viruses or other bugs that third parties may embed in or attach to this site without our knowledge or consent; (d) any software made available for downloading, copying or other use through this site; or (e) the merchantability, fitness for use, title and/or non-infringement of any or all of the contents of this site. 

Neither we nor anyone involved in the creation or delivery of this site or whose materials or information appear on this site shall have any liability (whether based on contract, tort, statute or otherwise) for any costs, losses, damages (whether direct, indirect, compensatory, special, lost profits, liquidated, consequential or punitive), arising out of or in connection with the your access to, browsing of or use of this site or any of the contents of this site.

**COPYRIGHT AND TRADEMARK NOTICE**  
This site is protected by U.S. copyright laws, and may be protected by the copyright laws of other countries and jurisdictions. Except as specifically permitted below, any copy, reproduction, display, performance or retransmission of the contents of this site is strictly prohibited. 

Any use of "Why Milk?," "whymilk.com," "Got Milk?" and any other trademarks, trade names and logos in which we, our subsidiaries, affiliates, divisions and licensors do business is strictly prohibited absent our prior written consent. In addition, the names, trade names and trademarks of third parties, including our promotional partners, that appear on this site are proprietary to their respective owners and may be used only with their express written permission. The mark and logo for "got milk?" is a registered trademark of the California Fluid Milk Processor Advisory Board.

**USE OF MILK MATERIALS**  
All of our proprietary documents, images, designs and information, including information about our businesses and other public information posted about our company on this site may be copied, reproduced, downloaded and used, provided that: (1) copyright notice in the form "© The National Milk Processor Promotion Board". Used With Permission. All rights reserved." appears on every copy or reproduction of such materials; (2) you only use these materials for non-commercial, personal purposes; (3) you do not alter, edit or condense these materials; and (4) you do not use these materials to ridicule, disparage, harass or annoy anyone.

If you would like to use, copy, upload or retransmit any of our proprietary materials, call or e-mail us to request written permission. The contents of this site may contain documents, images, information and other materials not proprietary to us, such as photographs, clip art, film clips, musical passages, audio track or sound effects elements, or the names, tradenames, trademarks, logos or designations of third parties. Any use whatsoever of any these non-Milk Materials is strictly prohibited, unless the prior written permission of the appropriate third parties has been secured. 

**YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS**  
By using this site, you signify your assent to the Milk Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our sites. Your continued use of the Milk sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Web site's privacy statement, you should first contact the company at whymilk@bsmg.com.
